commercebankfl.com 2016-04-11

# 

                                           PRIVACY NOTICE                                                      Rev. 9/2014
  FACTS
                       WHAT DOES MERCANTIL COMMERCEBANK, N.A.
                       DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
  Why?                 Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives
                       consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell
                       you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice
                       carefully to understand what we do.
  What?                The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service
                       you have with us. This information can include:
                              Social Security number            Transaction history
                              Account balances                  Checking account information
                       ■                                   ■
                              Credit history                    Wire transfer instructions
                       ■                                   ■
                       ■                                   ■
  How?                 All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday
                       business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their
                       customers’ personal information; the reasons Mercantil Commercebank, N.A.
                       chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
                                                                   Does Mercantil
  Reasons we can share your personal information                                           Can you limit this sharing?
                                                           Commercebank, N.A. share?
  For our everyday business purposes –
  such as to process your transactions, maintain
                                                                        Yes                           No
  your account(s), respond to court orders and legal
  investigations, or report to credit bureaus
  For our marketing purposes –
  to offer our products and services to you                             Yes                           No
  For joint marketing with other financial companies                     No                     We don’t share
  For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –
  information about your transactions and experiences                   Yes                           No
  For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –
  information about your creditworthiness                                No                     We don’t share
  For our affiliates to market to you                                   Yes                           Yes
  For nonaffiliates to market to you                                     No                     We don’t share
  To limit                   Mail the form below
  our sharing
                      ■
                      Please note:
                      If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we
                      sent this notice. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your informa-
                      tion as described in this notice.
                      However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
  Questions?          Call Toll-Free 1-888-629-0810 or go to www.mercantilcb.com
✃
  Mail-in Form
  If you have a         Mark any/all you want to limit:
  joint account,
                        ❑ Do not allow your affiliates to use my personal information to market to me.
  your choice(s)
  will apply to
  everyone on your      Name
  account unless
  you mark below.       Address
  ❑ Apply my
      choice(s) only    City, State, Zip
      to me.            Account #(s)
  Mail To:               Mercantil Commercebank, N.A.
                         Attn: Customer Service International
                         12496 NW 25th Street, Miami, FL 33182

  Page 2
   Who we are
   Who is providing this notice?          Mercantil Commercebank, N.A.
   What we do
   How does Mercantil Commercebank, N.A. To protect your personal information from unauthorized access
   protect my personal information?      and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.
                                         These measures include computer safeguards and secured files
                                         and buildings.
   How does Mercantil Commercebank, N.A. We collect your personal information, for example, when you
   collect my personal information?
                                               open an account                        deposit money
                                               provide account information            apply for a loan
                                         ■                                        ■
                                               use your credit or debit card
                                         ■                                        ■
                                         ■
                                         We also collect your personal information from others, such as
                                         credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
                                         Federal law gives you the right to limit only
   Why can’t I limit all sharing?
                                               sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes–information
                                               about your creditworthiness
                                         ■
                                               affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                               sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                                         ■
                                         ■
                                         State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights
                                         to limit sharing.
   What happens when I limit sharing     Your choices will apply to everyone on your account–unless you tell
   for an account I hold jointly with    us otherwise.
   someone else?
   Definitions
   Affiliates                            Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                         financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                               Our affiliates include financial companies such as Mercantil Banco
                                               Universal, Mercantil Commercebank Investment Services and
                                         ■
                                               Mercantil Commercebank Trust Company, N.A.
   Nonaffiliates                         Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can
                                         be financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                               Mercantil Commercebank, N.A. does not share with
                                               nonaffiliates so they can market to you.
                                         ■
   Joint marketing                       A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that
                                         together market financial products or services to you.
                                         ■     Mercantil Commercebank, N.A. does not jointly market.
 Member
 FDIC
✃
